Amanda Seale Show.
Today's
goes to
rapper Finesse Two Times
for successfully
finessing
two times.
So basically,
he sold the same verse to a
pair of artists, okay?
According to Finesse, one rapper didn't
pay to clear the verse, but the other one
did, which is why he ended up
with the bars too.
So he said, you can't get mad if I want to sell
my product to somebody else that you ain't paid for.
If I can do what I want to do with my verse,
how you gonna tell me what I can and what
I can't do with my verse? And y'all, he's
literally living up to his name. He told you
my name is Finesse Two Times.
So why would you
think you'd be exempt
from getting finessed
twice upon the day?
Don't mess with someone
named Beat'em Up Bobby. If you
don't want to risk getting beat up
by Bobby. Today's
let down. Goes to
Chinese marathon runners
who don't protect their
lungs. This guy, Uncle Chen
is known as the smoking brother. He's
a 52-year-old Chinese marathon runner
and he finished the Shaman
marathon while
chain smoking the entire
way. I'm looking at the runners
like, why did y'all not trip him?
It is hard enough to run a marathon.
But running through smoke, that's a different
beast, y'all.
We up, we up, we up.
We up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up, we up